Moritz Tomasi, Full-Stack Developer

I'm a full stack software engineer with experience in integrating many different tools and web frameworks together to develop a variety of different applications. I absolutely love programming, from designing system architecture for full stack apps to diving deep into frameworks and problem solving. I enjoy working on fun, collaborative teams that focus on optimization of applications and integrating additional features.

CONTACT

Lerchenfelderstrasse 129/4, 1070 Wien

J +43 650 72 72 959

f https://moritztomasi.github.io

In Moritz Tomasi

@MoritzTomasi

WORK EXPERIENCE

FINDHEIM GMBH

President | • | Nov. 2016 - Jun. 2018

I did stuff and things very nicely and everyone loved me to bits.

- Created features for an application that receives over one billion views per day
- Developed guest watch feature which increased the guest purchase rate by 5%
- Utilized Jest testing framework to increase code coverage from 37% to over 80%
- Resolved a large amount of accessibility bugs, reducing number of bugs by 65%

ZOOMSQUARE GMBH

President | • | Nov. 2016 - Jun. 2018

I did stuff and things very nicely and everyone loved me to bits.

- Developed Angular components, services, and directives, reusable through entire application
- Designed API endpoints to send & receive data from PostgreSQL database
- Implemented and optimized modular end-to-end features
- Wrote integration & unit tests for application routes using Mocha & Chai
- Utilized MongoDB to review logs, diagnose and resolve production bugs

EDUCATION

TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY OF VIENNA

Software Development Bachelor | 2009 - 2015

TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY OF VIENNA

Software Development Bachelor | 2009 - 2015

COMPETENCIES

- NodeJS, Python
- Javascript, Typescript
- VueJS (NuxtJS), React
- AWS, elastic.co
- Elasticsearch, Postgres, Redis
- Machine Learning, NLP, Computer Vision
- GIS (PostGIS, QGIS)

LANGUAGES

- German (mothertongue)
- English (fluent)
- Italian (fluent)